<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Certificate Transparency</title>
    <link>https://certificate.transparency.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Certificate Transparency</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://certificate.transparency.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://certificate.transparency.dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 15:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://certificate.transparency.dev/</guid>
      <description>Working together to detect maliciously or mistakenly issued certificates.          An ecosystem that makes the issuance of website certificates transparent and verifiable.    To the participants of the Certificate Transparency (CT) ecosystem, who give their time, expertise, and resources to help keep the web secure.                             Thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://certificate.transparency.dev/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://certificate.transparency.dev/community/</guid>
      <description>Our Story Thank you to our amazing community  Certificate Transparency works thanks to the ecosystem of people and organizations who set up and run user agents, logs and monitors. Join us!
 Join Google Group         Our origin story  Certificate Transparency was a response to the 2011 attack on DigiNotar and other Certificate Authorities. These attacks showed that the lack of transparency in the way CAs operated was a significant risk to the Web Public Key Infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google / Known Logs</title>
      <link>https://certificate.transparency.dev/google/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://certificate.transparency.dev/google/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Known Logs Special Purpose Logs Mirrors Test Logs  Known Logs Lists of known CT Logs are maintained by each CT-enforcing user agent.
Learn more about the list of CT Logs that are currently compliant with Chrome&amp;rsquo;s CT policy (or have been and were disqualified) at https://googlechrome.github.io/CertificateTransparency/log_lists.html
Special Purpose Logs  https://ct.googleapis.com/daedalus/ Base64 Log ID: HQJLjrFJizRN/YfqPvwJlvdQbyNdHUlwYaR3PEOcJfs= Operator: Google Contact: google-ct-logs@googlegroups.com  Daedalus is not trusted by CT-enforcing user agents such as Chrome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How CT Works</title>
      <link>https://certificate.transparency.dev/howctworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://certificate.transparency.dev/howctworks/</guid>
      <description>How CT works How CT fits into the wider Web PKI ecosystem  Contents:  Certificate Transparency: an ecosystem Certificate Transparency: step by step How Certificate Transparency fits in Web Public Key Infrastructure        Certificate Transparency: an ecosystem Certificates are deposited in public, transparent logs Certificate logs are append-only ledgers of certificates. Because they&#39;re distributed and independent, anyone can query them to see what certificates have been included and when.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logs</title>
      <link>https://certificate.transparency.dev/logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://certificate.transparency.dev/logs/</guid>
      <description>Logs The list of current, usable logs  Certificate Transparency logs are &#34;append-only&#34; and publicly-auditable ledgers of certificates being created, updated, and expired.
Go to Monitors Go to User Agents                                                               Add your Log to this list</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitors</title>
      <link>https://certificate.transparency.dev/monitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://certificate.transparency.dev/monitors/</guid>
      <description>Monitors The list of existing monitors  Monitors make sure that all logged certificates are visible in the log and watch for suspicious certificates in logs
Go to Logs Go to User Agents          Identify expired or misconfigured SSL/TLS certificates and track vendor compliance.         Get an email every time a certificate is issued for one of your monitored domains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Agents</title>
      <link>https://certificate.transparency.dev/useragents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://certificate.transparency.dev/useragents/</guid>
      <description>User Agents User agents using CT  User agents are typically browsers and help perform certificate auditing by verifying that certificates have legitimately been added to a log.
Go to Logs Go to Monitors          Google Chrome Supporting CT since early 2015         Apple Safari Supporting CT since 2018         Brave Supporting CT since 2023         Firefox Supporting CT since 2025         Android Supporting CT since 2025       Add CT to your user agent</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
